[Music]
you know horses the horse and cart for
who rises
when uniform parking order order and I'm
scared that I talk too much about what I
think's going on got away with this they
might grab me the winner
so my patron is to just say what I
bought like I made for this but I'm
afraid as I might be bought
maybe that's why I'm here might get
along
for the time but we both get a strange
sound coming sounds like war and it
breaks our hearts when I started this
game didn't have no plans hit Espino art
just run with the crab of a couple last
place [ __ ] - yeah
get a little tap like and the [ __ ]
dead hair maybe give a little big the
genie for your dream and cleaning bomb
hostels joy speak with the powder smile
possible
okay Susan our faith and imagine I will
not be confused adopts a la crema
[Music]
we meet Russ is [ __ ] up enough shame
anybody drug rub the devil don't sleep
either
people eater gladiators that appalls off
please come until it on a new world for
private a to school for the world war
and the apocalypse later on for turn
around the air
until is over I'm a house
may have Sarah
[Music]
[Applause]
mere mortals the dogs coming so misty
with the war people you take the devil
for God look how you doing you I'm Jack
Johnson I be this way capture snap the
truth Michael flowers with a higher
power happy life against the bad to feel
like killing baby be mine Tyson punch
this is bad news
so feel me follow me on top of this
lifeless press you like Orson Welles on
a radio or ask the world a world of make
all your famous go
I need the greatest imperfect work in
our brains you know
can't wait to load up the silos and make
your pages blow
abuses you beg somebody to roofie you to
stand your hope up and use it like it's
a hula hoop and interleukin talking
they're just like their will let's do
this
[Music]
just kill you
you
[Music]
remaining space predictive I can't erase
kill you
just
[Music]